# **AMIT LEVINSON**

I am an MA student in the Sociology & Anthropology Department at Ben-Gurion University of the negev. I am currently researching illegal drug markets and technology with a focus on the online Israeli cannabis market on Telegram. In my spare time I like to learn and visualize in R.

#### **EDUCATION**

2020 2018

# MA, Sociology & Anthropology

Page Be'er-Sheva, Israel

**Ben-Gurion University** 

- Currently enrolled (expected 2020)
- Thesis: Exploring the authentication process in the online Israeli illegal drug market

2018 2015

# BA, Sociology, Anthropology & Political Science

Be'er-Sheva, Israel

**Ben-Gurion University** 

· Magna cum laude

### SKILLS

L⊞ R. SPSS

CONTACT

■ amitlevinson1@gmail.com

@ amitlevinson.com Amit\_Levinson

in Amit Levinson

**★** Amit\_Levinson

☐ Microsoft Office



#### EXPERIENCE

2020 2018

#### **Research Assistant**

**Department of Political Science** 

**♀** Ben-Gurion University

- · Online and Offline political participation research assistant for Dr. Jennifer Oser
- English-language research and literature survey
- Statistical coding and interpretation of literature

2017 2016

#### Creative campaign manager **Ben-Gurion Student Union**

**♀** Ben-Gurion University

• Event branding and management of professional photographer team

2015 2013

## Israeli Liaison for the Jewish Agency

Rockville JCC

Rockville, MD, USA

- Jewish Community Center: Event planning and promotion; Activity management; Presentations
- · Operational responsibility for the Israeli Scouts local chapter



**SPSS Workshop Conductor** 2020-Department of Sociology & Anthropology, BA  $\P$  Ben-Gurion University 04 2019-10 · Reviewed assignments, provided feedback and guidance for using **SPSS Statistics Teaching Assistant** 2020 Department of Sociology & Anthropology, BA  $\P$  Ben-Gurion University 2018 • Taught for two semesters · Independent presentations; Assisting individual students; Test writing **Quantitative Methods Teaching Assistant** 2019-10 Department of Sociology & Anthropology, BA igoplus Ben-Gurion University 2019-04 • Independent presentations; Assisting individual students; Test writing **TALKS** Wrangling and visualizing data in R 2020-04 Online Zoom Israel-2050 Fellows program "Yes I can...?" Political efficacy in the digital era 2020-03 Page Be'er-Sheva, Israel • Presented at Revolutions and Counter-revolutions: Ben-Gurion University Social Science and Humanities Annual Conference • Co-Presented with Dr. Jennifer Oser & Dr Shelley Boulianne 2019-10 **Teaching Assistants Work Shop** Page Be'er-Sheva, Israel Department of Sociology & Anthropology, BGU · Co-Presented with Eliza Frenkel Digital Media Use, Political Participation & Political Efficacy: A Research 2019-05 Agenda. Akko, Israel Israel Political Science Association conference · Co-Presented with Dr. Jennifer Oser Conducting a Seminar Paper for B.A students 2019-01 Be'er-Sheva, Israel Department of Politics and Government, BGU · Presented at the seminar course "Democratization and De-Democratization in Contemporary Russia"



2012 Armored Corps 2009

**♀** Israel